contentblvd.com 2015-03-15

# Content BLVD PRIVACY POLICY - Content BLVD

## PRIVACY POLICY

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to ContentBLVD.com and Content Blvd, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Content Blvd, Inc. include ContentBLVD.com and Content BLVD. The Content BLVD website is a business networking and ecommerce site. By using the Content BLVD website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

Content BLVD may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Content BLVD's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. Content BLVD may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income and race. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Content BLVD. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Content BLVD website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Content BLVD's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Content BLVD encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Content BLVD so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Content BLVD is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Content BLVD website.

Use of your Personal Information

Content BLVD collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Content BLVD may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Content BLVD and its affiliates. Content BLVD may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Content BLVD does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Content BLVD may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. Content BLVD may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Content BLVD, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Content BLVD may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Content BLVD, in order to determine what Content BLVD services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Content BLVD to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Content BLVD will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Content BLVD or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Content BLVD; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Content BLVD, or the public.

Use of Cookies

The Content BLVD website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Content BLVD pages, or register with Content BLVD site or services, a cookie helps Content BLVD to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Content BLVD website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Content BLVD features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Content BLVD services or websites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

Content BLVD secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

Children Under Thirteen

Content BLVD does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

Disconnecting your Content BLVD Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your Content BLVD account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR CONTENT BLVD ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their "My Account" page. Users may also contact us via email or telephone.

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Content BLVD by contacting us here:

\- Web page: ContentBLVD.com/contact-us

\- Email: support@contentblvd.com

\- Phone: 305-801-3747

Changes to this Statement

Content BLVD will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Content BLVD encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Content BLVD is protecting your information.

Contact Information

Content BLVD welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Content BLVD has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Content BLVD at:

Content Blvd, Inc.

1730 S Hayworth Ave

Los Angeles, California 90035

Email Address:

support@contentblvd.com

Telephone number:

305-801-3747

Effective as of September 01, 2014
